newzfind.com 2006-05-05

# 

NewzFind PRIVACY POLICY

We at Harizma, Inc. understand that your privacy is very important to you. That's why we've developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using NewzFind. 

Table of Contents  
A Special Note About Children  
About Newzfind and Information We Collect  
Our Disclosure of Your Information  
Control of Your Passworr  
Security  
Update/Delete

1\. A Special Note About Children  
Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We ask that children not submit information to us.

2\. About NewzFind and Information We Collect  
NewzFind is an online classified which provides you useful tools to find files stored on variuos filesharing resources. Newzfind is FREE to all qualified members.

In our online ANONYMOUS registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your Nick and Password. However, NONE of the personally identifiable information can be accessed or used by the public to identify a specific individual.

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites automatically collect this information. If you choose to post messages in our Comments, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal.

3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information  
We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. 

4\. Control of Your Password  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

5\. Security NewzFind has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. NewzFind uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at NewzFind work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.

10\. Update/Delete  
NewzFind Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database:

* Send an email to Customer Service;  
NewzFind PRIVACY POLICY  
Effective on: (01/01/06)
